# RAMADAN MUSTAPHA

Web developer



## **PROFILE**

A dedicated Web developer having good knowledge in PHP Laravel and Symfony. I like to write clean.scalable and bug free code I have a good eye for design and can provide business insights based on my experience and working with my friends.

### **SKILLS**

- PHP, C#, JavaScript, Python.
- .Net, Laravel, Symfony, Vue, JQuery, BootStrap, Node js.
- SQL, MySQL.
- UNIX, Shell, Git Hub, REST API.

## **LANGUES**

- Arabic
- English
- ••••
- French

# **INTERESTS**

- Self- learning
- New Technologies
- Sport
- Travel

# **QUALITIES**

- Autonomy
- Creativity
- Negotiation
- Organisation

### **EDUCATION**

- 2023: Study Full Stack Software Engineering | Back-end ALX.
- 2021: Diploma Specialist Technician Diploma in Computer Development. ISTA Hay Salam, Sale.
- 2017: Bachelor's Degree in Fundamental Law, specializing in Private Law. University Mohammed V
- 2013: High School Diploma in Experimental Sciences. High School Almotanabi. Sale.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

• Mar.2022 - Dec.2023, Sale, Morocco.

Full-stack Developer.

Freelancer Developer.

• Oct.2023 - Dec.2023, Rabat, Morocco.

Web Developer.

Internship at an International Academy for the development of information and communication.

• Mar.2023 - Sep.2023, Rabat, Morocco.

Full-stack Developer.

Internship within a 218LABS company.

Mission: Development of web application projects, modification and creation of structured scripts, dealing with databases..

Technology: PHP, MySQL, API, JQuery, Laravel, Symfony.

• Avr.2021 - juill.2021, Rabat, Morocco.

Full-stack Developer.

Internship within the Information Systems Division, Department of Public Enterprises and Privatization.

Mission: Creation and development of an Intranet website.

Technology: Asp.net, SQL, JS, Bootstrap, HTML, CSS.

#### PROJECTS PROFESSIONNELLE

MustaphaRam/Resume\_cv (github.com)

Create a web application using Laravel and Vue js, to help you create and download online their resume in a stylish and professional way.

MustaphaRam/screenShot (github.com)

This project is a web application built with Symfony and Vue.J. S. It allows users to capture screenshots of websites by providing the URL and specifying the desired image size.

MustaphaRam/AirBnB clone v4 (github.com)

Create a web application, similar to the AirBnB site to save hotel rooms, developed using python, Flask RESTful API.